Guide to the Robert M. Rosenzweig, Vice Provost of Stanford University, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Records
  - Language and Area Centers, National Defense Foreign Language Fellowships (NDFL), 1970-1974 (Box 9)
  - African Language and Area Center, NDFL, 1966-1970 (Box 9)
  - NDFL, E. Asian Languages Summer Program, 1968-1970 (Box 9)
  - East Asian Library Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 9)
  - NDFL, Latin American Language and Area Center, 1968-1970 (Box 9)
  - NDFL, Stanford-Warsaw Exchange, 1966-1971 (Box 9)
  - Russian and East European Languages, 1970 (Box 9)
  - Graduate Division - Leverhulme Fellowship, 1966-1971 (Box 10)
  - NDFL Proposals, 1968-1969 (Box 10)
  - State Department Fellows at Stanford, 1969-1972 (Box 10)
  - Mark J. Garrison, State Department Fellow, 1970-1971 (Box 10)
  - Richard D. Nethercut, State Department Fellow, 1970-1971 (Box 10)
  - Donald R. Norland, State Department Fellow, 1969-1970 (Box 10)
  - John D. Negroponte, State Department Fellow, 1969-1970 (Box 10)
  - John F. Knowles, State Department Fellow, 1972-1973 (Box 10)
  - Francis J. McNeil, State Department Fellow, 1971-1972 (Box 10)
  - J. Bruce Amstutz, State Department Fellow, 1971-1972 (Box 10)
  - Hoover Institution, 1971-1974 (Box 10)
  - Low Cost Housing on campus, File I, 1968 Sep-1969 Aug (Box 10)
  - Cofield-Goldman, Sachs, 1970 (Box 10)
  - Houston, Texas Meeting, 1971 (Box 10)
  - Denver, Colorado Meeting, 1971 (Box 10)
  - Stanford-Czechoslovakia Exchange, 1969 (Box 10)
  - Yugoslav Seminar, CRIS, 1969-1970 (Box 10)
  - Committee on International Studies, 1970-1971 (Box 10)
  - International Studies, Center for Research in, 1968-1969 (Box 10)
  - International Studies, Center for Research in, 1969-1970 (Box 10)
  - Committee on International Studies, 1971-1973 (Box 10)
  - NDEA Centers, 1971-1972 (Box 10)
  - International Studies, 1972-1974 (Box 10)
  - International Studies, Conferences and Meetings, 1971-1972 (Box 10)
  - I.S. Director's Search-Robert Ward, 1972-1973 (Box 10)
  - I.S. Director's Search-Outside Nominations, 1972-1973 (Box 10)
  - I.S. Director's Search-Inside Nominations, 1972-1973 (Box 10)
  - International Studies, Research Commitments, 1972-1973 (Box 10)
  - International Studies, Salaries, 1971-1972 (Box 10)
  - Latin American Studies, 1968-1973 (Box 10)
  - Commission on East Asian Studies (Dien, Lewis, Li, Skinner, Van Slyke), 1972 (Box 10)
  - Inter-University Center for Japanese Language Studies in Tokyo, 1969-1973 (Box 10)
  - Higher Education Act, 1968-1971 (Box 10)
  - HUD Proposal, 1969-1970 (Box 10)
  - Low Cost Housing on campus, File II, 1969 Sep-1970 Aug (Box 10)
  - International Studies, Center for Research in, CRIS, 1970-1971 (Box 10)
  - Medical School, 1969-1973 (Box 10)
  - Overseas Campuses, 1967-1973 (Box 11)
  - President's Staff, 1971 (Box 11)
  - President's Office and Staff, Meetings, 1970-1971 (Box 11)
  - President's Office and Staff, 1965-1970 (Box 11)
  - Legal Advisor to the President (Office of), 1970 (Box 11)
  - Provost's Staff-Organizations, Appts., 1967-1970 (Box 11)
  - Investments, Committee on, Trustees, 1970-1971 (Box 11)
  - Board of Trustees, List of Members, 1965-1971 (Box 11)
  - Board of Trustees, General, 1971-1972 (Box 11)
  - Board of Trustees, 1968-1971 (Box 11)
  - Term Papers, 1969 (Box 11)
  - Provost's Staff-Organizations, Appts., 1970-1971 (Box 11)
  - "Education in Singapore", 1966 (Box 11)
  - Singapore Polytechnic, 1965-1967 (Box 11)
  - Ateneo de Manila University, 1966-1967 (Box 11)
  - C.R.I.S., M. Karsulin Proposal, Yugo. Acad. Of Arts and Sci., 1968 (Box 11)
  - Seminar in Yugoslavia, Correspondence, 1968 Summer (Box 11)
  - Seminar in Yugoslavia, Correspondence re: Participants, 1966-1967 (Box 11)
  - Seminar in Yugoslavia, General, 1967 (Box 11)
  - Seminar in Yugoslavia, American Studies, 1966 (Box 11)
  - Richard Bell (Ampex), 1968 (Box 11)
  - Jose Benitez, 1968 (Box 11)
  - Howard Brooks, 1967-1968 (Box 11)
  - Arthur P. Coladarci, 1967-1968 (Box 11)
  - Kenneth Creighton, 1968 (Box 11)
  - Paul R. Hanna - Memos, etc., 1968 (Box 11)
  - Paul R. Hanna - Correspondence-Trip, 1967 (Box 11)
  - Robert M. Rosenzweig - Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 11)
  - Inter-University Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 11)
  - Hanna-USOE Contacts, 1967 (Box 11)
  - Asian Seminar, Program, 1968 (Box 11)
  - Memos to Participants, 1968 (Box 11)
  - Asian Seminar, Proceedings, 1968 (Box 11)
  - Asian Seminar, Newspaper articles, 1968 (Box 11)
  - Stanford/Asia Foundation Reception, 1968 (Box 11)
  - Asian Seminar, Korean Letter of Invitation-drafts, 1968 (Box 11)
  - Asian Seminar, Calendar, 1968 (Box 11)
  - Asian Seminar, Non-Stanford Consultant, 1968 (Box 11)
  - Asian Seminar, Statement: Stanford University, 1968 (Box 11)
  - Asian Seminar, Accomodations, 1968 (Box 11)
  - Paul R. Hanna - Itinerary, Undated (Box 11)
  - Travel Arrangements, 1968 (Box 11)
  - Asian Seminar, Travel - Bell, 1968 (Box 11)
  - Asian Seminar, Travel - Benitez, 1968 (Box 11)
  - Asian Seminar, Travel - Brooks, 1968 (Box 11)
  - Asian Seminar, Travel - Creighton, 1968 (Box 11)
  - Asian Seminar, Travel - Hanna, 1968 (Box 11)
  - Asian Seminar, Travel - Rosenzweig, 1968 (Box 11)
  - Asian Seminar, Travel - Mothershead, 1968 (Box 11)
  - Asian Seminar - List of Participants, 1968 (Box 11)
  - Arthur Coladarci, 1967-1968 (Box 11)
  - Asia Foundation - Directory of Offices, 1966-1968 (Box 11)
  - Asian Seminar - TAF Program Quarterly, 1968 (Box 11)
  - Asian Seminar - Final Report, 1968 (Box 11)
  - Asia Foundation - Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 11)
  - William Volckhausen, Correspondence, 1968 (Box 11)
  - Patricia Flanagan, Correspondence, 1968 (Box 11)
  - Glen Bowersox, Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 11)
  - Easton Rothwell, 1968 (Box 11)
  - Asian Seminar, Minutes of Meetings, Stanford, 1968 (Box 11)
  - Asian Seminar, Minutes of Meetings with TAF/SF, 1968 (Box 11)
  - Meeting on the Asian Seminar, 1968 Feb 28 (Box 11)
  - Asia Foundation/Stanford Meeting, Stanford Faculty Club, 1968 Jan 22 (Box 11)
  - Minutes of Meetings with the Asia Foundation, 1967 (Box 11)
  - Asian Seminar, TAF/Korea, Correspondence, 1968 (Box 11)
  - Asian Seminar, A.I.R.C., Correspondence, 1968 (Box 11)
  - Asian Seminar, Korea, General Correspondence, 1968 (Box 11)
  - Korea, 1968 (Box 11)
  - AIRC Proposals and Plans, 1968 Feb (Box 11)
  - Asian Seminar, TAF/Philippines, Correspondence, 1968 (Box 11)
  - Philippines, 1967-1968 (Box 11)
  - Asian Seminar, Philippines, General Correspondence, 1968 (Box 11)
  - Asian Seminar, TAF/Taiwan, Correspondence, 1968 (Box 11)
  - Asian Seminar, Taiwan, General Correspondence, 1968 (Box 11)
  - Taiwan, 1968 (Box 11)
  - The Ford Foundation, 1968 (Box 11)
  - Seminar: "The Role of Higher Education in National Development in Asia," Seoul, Korea, 1968 Aug 9-23 (Box 12)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1968 (Box 12)
  - UNESCO, 1968 (Box 12)
  - John Brohm, 1967-1968 (Box 12)
  - William Eilers, 1968 (Box 12)
  - Howard Jones, 1968 (Box 12)
  - Albert L. Seely-United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia, 1968 (Box 12)
  - Asian Seminar, Stanford Letters to Participants, 1968 (Box 12)
  - Asian Seminar, Did not attend, 1968 (Box 12)
  - Asian Seminar, Cicero D. Calderon (Philippines), 1968 (Box 12)
  - Asian Seminar, Tan Chang (Taiwan), 1968 (Box 12)
  - Asian Seminar, Mun-Whan Choe (Korea), 1968 (Box 12)
  - Asian Seminar, Bom-Mo Chung (Korea), 1968 (Box 12)
  - Asian Seminar, Antonio Isidro (Philippines), 1968 (Box 12)
  - Asian Seminar, Tai-Kuang Kang (Taiwan), 1968 (Box 12)
  - Asian Seminar, Kwangman Kauh (Korea), 1968 (Box 12)
  - Asian Seminar, Jong Chul Kim (Korea), 1968 (Box 12)
  - Asian Seminar, Okgill Kim (Korea), 1968 (Box 12)
  - Asian Seminar, Chin Kao Lee (Taiwan), 1968 (Box 12)
  - Asian Seminar, Chong-Woo Lee (Korea), 1968 (Box 12)
  - Asian Seminar, Hahn-Been Lee (Korea), 1968 (Box 12)
  - Asian Seminar, Hui Sok Mun, Correspondence, 1968 (Box 12)
  - Asian Seminar, Isjrin Noerdin, Indonesia, 1968 (Box 12)
  - Asian Seminar, Hyun Ki Paik (Korea), 1968 (Box 12)
  - Asian Seminar, Tae Sun Park (Korea), 1968 (Box 12)
  - Asian Seminar, Waldo Perfecto (Philippines), 1968 (Box 12)
  - Asian Seminar, Carl F. Bartz, American Embassy, 1968 (Box 12)
  - Asian Seminar, Marie C. Berger (United Board for Christian Higher Ed. In Asia), 1968 (Box 12)
  - Asian Seminar, Clifford Liddle (USOM), 1968 (Box 12)
  - Asian Seminar, Herbert Long (East-West Center), 1968 (Box 12)
  - Asian Seminar, Chung-Hyun Ro (Korea), 1968 (Box 12)
  - Asian Seminar, Bascomb Storey (USOM), 1968 (Box 12)
  - Asian Seminar, Background Materials, 1968 (Box 12)
  - Asian Seminar, Opening Paper, Paul R. Hanna, 1968 (Box 12)
  - Asian Seminar, First Paper, Topic 1, Hyun Ki Paik, 1968 (Box 12)
  - Asian Seminar, First Paper, Topic 2, Hahn Been Lee, 1968 (Box 12)
  - Asian Seminar, First Paper, Topic 3, Bom-Mo Chung, 1968 (Box 12)
  - Asian Seminar, Sun Pan-cheng (Taiwan), 1968 (Box 12)
  - Asian Seminar, Second Paper, Topic 2, Kenneth Creighton, 1968 (Box 12)
  - Asian Seminar, Second Paper, Topic 3, Howard Brooks, 1968 (Box 12)
  - Asian Seminar, Special Paper, Topic 3, Richard Bell, 1968 (Box 12)
  - Asian Seminar, Concluding Statement, C. Easton Rothwell, 1968 (Box 12)
  - Asian Seminar, Rapporteur's Reports, Topic 1, 1968 (Box 12)
  - Asian Seminar, Rapporteur's Reports, Topic 2, 1968 (Box 12)
  - Asian Seminar, Rapporteur's Reports, Topic 3, 1968 (Box 12)
  - Asian Seminar, Republic of China National Group Report, 1968 (Box 12)
  - Asian Seminar, Indonesian Report, 1968 (Box 12)
  - Papers - Republic of China, 1968 (Box 12)
  - Afghanistan, 1967-1968 (Box 12)
  - Asian Seminar, TAF/Afghanistan, Correspondence, 1968 (Box 12)
  - Ceylon, 1967 (Box 12)
  - Asian Seminar, TAF/Ceylon, Correspondence, 1968 (Box 12)
  - Hong Kong, 1967-1968 (Box 12)
  - India, 1967-1968 (Box 12)
  - Asian Seminar, TAF/India, Correspondence, 1968 (Box 12)
  - Indonesia, 1967-1968 (Box 12)
  - Iran, 1967-1968 (Box 12)
  - Asian Seminar, TAF/Japan, Correspondence, 1968 (Box 12)
  - Japan, 1967-1968 (Box 12)
  - Malaysia, 1967 (Box 12)
  - Asian Seminar, TAF/Malaysia, Correspondence, 1968 (Box 12)
  - Singapore, 1967-1968 (Box 12)
  - Asian Seminar, TAF/Thailand, Correspondence, 1968 (Box 12)
  - Vietnam, 1968 (Box 12)
  - Asian Seminar, TAF/Vietnam, Correspondence, 1968 (Box 12)
  - Proceedings of TAF Conference on University Cooperation and Asian Development - Hong Kong, 1966 Dec 18-21 (Box 12)
  - Asia Foundation/Stanford Seminar, General Agreement, 1967 Jan 11 (Box 12)
  - Wert-Asia Foundation/Stanford Seminar Finances: Appeals for New Funds, 1966 (Box 12)
  - Wert's General Notes, Asia Foundation/Stanford Seminar, 1966-1967 (Box 12)
  - Mr. Wert's Handwritten Notes-Save, 1967 (Box 12)
  - Wert/Asia Foundation-Letters, Minutes of Meetings, etc., 1965-1967 (Box 12)
  - Miscellaneous Articles, 1965-1966 (Box 12)
  - Report on Jones' Visit to Tokyo, Seoul, Taipei, Manila, Bangkok, and Hong Kong, 1967 (Box 12)
  - General Info. On Accounts, 1968-1970 (Box 12)
  - Research-Proposals submitted, academic year, 1969-1970 (Box 12)
  - Research-Proposals submitted, academic year, 1968-1969 (Box 12)
  - Davis, Noel Gregson G., 1968-1969 (Box 12)
  - "Leadership Development Program in Higher Education," Doug Davis Proposals, Research, 1969 (Box 12)
  - Research Administration, 1969 Sep-1970 Aug (Box 12)
  - Research Administration, 1967 Nov-1969 Aug (Box 12)
  - Grants terminated; final reports-research, 1969 (Box 12)
  - Grants continuing, research proposals, 1968-1970 (Box 12)
  - Research Proposals-Support denied, 1969-1970 (Box 12)
  - General Secretary's Office, Foundations, 1969-1970 (Box 12)
  - Interim Report on Government Research Projects, 1967-1968 (Box 12)
  - Government Grants received, Research Administration, 1967-1968 (Box 12)
  - International Studies, 1974-1975 (Box 13)
  - CRIS-Center for Research in International Studies, 1974 (Box 13)
  - Fellowship Programs/CRIS, 1974 (Box 13)
  - Advisory Com. To the Director of the Center for Research in International Studies, 1974 (Box 13)
  - Commission on International Studies, 1973 (Box 13)
  - International Studies Budget, 1973 (Box 13)
  - International Center in San Francisco/Proposal, 1974 (Box 13)
  - Hoover International Studies Bldg. (see Hoover III Building), 1972 (Box 13)
  - DAAD Program, 1971-1974 (Box 13)
  - United States-China Relations Program, 1974 (Box 13)
  - Chinese Language Studies in Taipei, Inter-Univ. Program in, 1973 (Box 13)
  - Tanaka Endowment/Japan Found.: see Japan Foundation File, Undated (Box 13)
  - Japanese Art, International Studies, 1972-1973 (Box 13)
  - Japanese Studies at Stanford, 1973-1974 (Box 13)
  - Inter-Univ. Center for Japanese Language Studies in Tokyo, 1973-1974 (Box 13)
  - Joint Chinese-Japanese Language and Area Center in Chinese and Japanese at Stanford and U. of C., 1973-1974 (Box 13)
  - Committee on Latin American Studies, 1973-1974 (Box 13)
  - Russian and East European Studies, 1971-1974 (Box 13)
  - East Asian Library Committee (see also: Mellon Foundation), 1973-1974 (Box 13)
  - East Asian Studies Program, 1972-1974 (Box 13)
  - International Studies-Roxane Witke Proposal, 1972 (Box 13)
  - Survey, 1970-1973 (Box 13)
  - I.S. Director's Search: William B. Bader, 1972-1973 (Box 13)
  - International Studies-Director's Search, 1972-1973 (Box 13)
  - I.S.: Administration, 1965-1971 (Box 13)
  - International Relations-Director's Search, 1972 (Box 13)
  - Lederer Committee, 1971 (Box 13)
  - Committee on the Future Int. Studies, 1970-1972 (Box 13)
  - International Studies-Mihailo Mihailov, 1972-1973 (Box 13)
  - RMR Director of CRIS, 1972-1973 (Box 13)
  - CRIS-Journal of International Studies, 1970-1972 (Box 13)
  - Ford Arms Control Proposal, 1972-1973 (Box 13)
  - Ford Foundation, European and Canadian Affairs, 1971-1972 (Box 13)
  - Ford, Center for Research in Economic Growth, 1972 (Box 13)
  - International Studies/FORD, 1971 (Box 13)
  - Ford Transitional Grant Negotiations, 1971-1972 (Box 13)
  - International Studies Grants, Individual Faculty Members, 1970-1972 (Box 13)
  - Japan Fund, 1972 (Box 13)
  - East Asia: Peals Project, Wolf, Skinner and Lewis, 1970-1971 (Box 13)
  - Portuguese, 1973 Summer (Box 13)
  - Slavic Summer Program, International Studies, 1966-1970 (Box 13)
  - Chinese Language Studies in Taipei, Inter-Univ. Program in, 1970-1973 (Box 13)
  - CRIS-Center for Research in International Studies, 1972-1974 (Box 13)
  - C.R.I.S., SIDEC, 1967-1968 (Box 13)
  - C.R.I.S., Wingspread Conference (EWA), 1968 Mar 12-13 (Box 13)
  - C.R.I.S., Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 13)
  - C.R.I.S., Latin American Educ'l Dev't, Richard Richardsom, 1967-1968 (Box 13)
  - C.R.I.S., International Education Act, 1966 (Box 13)
  - I.S.-Russel G. Davis Report, 1968 (Box 13)
  - C.R.I.S., Miscellaneous, 1971-1972 (Box 13)
  - Student Initiated Research-Research, 1969-1970 (Box 14)
  - "Research and Training Opportunities Abroad", 1970-1971 (Box 14)
  - Institute for the Study of Human Problems-Research, 1969 (Box 14)
  - Faculty/Research Study Projects-Research, 1969 (Box 14)
  - Proposal to Ford Foundation, Academic Planning Office, 1970 (Box 14)
  - Analyses of Gift Pledges, Foundations, Undated (Box 14)
  - Proposed tax on foundations, 1969 (Box 14)
  - Foundations, General, 1968-1970 (Box 14)
  - ARCS Foundation, 1973 (Box 14)
  - Asia Foundation, 1967-1974 (Box 14)
  - Foundations, A-, 1968-1970 (Box 14)
  - Foundations, B-, 1969 (Box 14)
  - Foundations, C-, 1969-1972 (Box 14)
  - Foundations, Carnegie Corp. of New York, 1969-1970 (Box 14)
  - Foundations, Commission on Foundations and Philanthropy (Peterson), 1969 (Box 14)
  - Foundations, D, 1968-1969 (Box 14)
  - Arthur Vining Davis Foundation, 1968-1970 (Box 14)
  - Foundations, E, 1968-1970 (Box 14)
  - Foundations, F, 1968-1969 (Box 14)
  - Ford Foundation, 1972-1974 (Box 14)
  - Ford Foundation, 1971-1972 (Box 14)
  - Ford Foundation, 1970 Sep-1971 Aug (Box 14)
  - PEALS Proposal-Ford Foundation, 1970 (Box 14)
  - Ford Foundation, 1969 May-Aug (Box 14)
  - Ford Foundation, 1968 Sep-1969 Apr (Box 14)
  - Ford Foundation-Grants awarded, 1969-1971 (Box 14)
  - Foundations, G, 1969 (Box 14)
  - Grant Foundation, 1969-1970 (Box 14)
  - Foundations, H, 1969 (Box 14)
  - Hartford Foundation, 1969-1971 (Box 14)
  - Hewlett Foundation, 1974 (Box 14)
  - Foundations, I, Undated (Box 14)
  - Foundations, J, Undated (Box 14)
  - Japan Foundation, 1973-1974 (Box 14)
  - Johnson Foundation, 1974 (Box 14)
  - Foundations, K, 1968-1970 (Box 14)
  - Foundations, Klein Fund, 1968-1969 (Box 14)
  - Foundations, L, 1968-1970 (Box 14)
  - Foundations, M, 1968-1970 (Box 14)
  - The Luce Foundation, 1969-1971 (Box 14)
  - Luce Foundation-International Studies, 1971-1972 (Box 14)
  - The Henry Luce Foundation Scholars Program, 1973-1974 (Box 14)
  - Mellon Foundation, 1971-1974 (Box 14)
  - Merrill Trust Fund, 1968-1970 (Box 14)
  - Mitsubishi Group, 1974 (Box 14)
  - Foundations, Rockefeller, 1968-1974 (Box 14)
  - Seeley Mudd Educational Trust, 1968-1969 (Box 14)
  - National Endowment for Humanities, 1971-1972 (Box 14)
  - N.S.F. (National Science Foundation), 1970-1971 (Box 14)
  - Foundations, O, 1969 (Box 14)
  - Foundations, P, Undated (Box 14)
  - Foundations, R, 1969 (Box 14)
  - Research Corporation, 1969 (Box 14)
  - Smith Richardson Foundation, 1973 (Box 14)
  - Spencer Foundation, 1974 (Box 14)
  - Foundations, S, 1968-1974 (Box 14)
  - Foundations, Shell Oil, 1969-1970 (Box 14)
  - The Zellerbach Foundation, 1969-1970 (Box 14)
  - Westinghouse-Tretiak Study, Campus Conflict, with Brandeis, 1970-1971 (Box 14)
  - Foundations, W, 1969 (Box 14)
  - School of Humanities and Sciences: "A Report on Academic Space from 1963-64 through 1974-75", 1963-1975 (Box 14)
  - East European Trip, 1966 Aug (Box 14)
  - Consortium of Western Universities, 1970-1971 (Box 14)